probioticamerica.com 2017-11-15

# Probiotic America | Privacy Policy

### Your Consent

By using the Website, you consent to the collection and use of certain information in the manner we describe and agree to be bound by the terms of use as set forth herein. By logging into your cart, you consent to periodic email notifications regarding the status of your checkout process. You may opt out of these any time after your initial notice.

### Notification of Changes

The practices and policies contained in this Policy are subject to change at any time without prior notice. If we decide to change our policies, we will post those changes on this Website. Information collected before changes are made will be secured according to the Policy in place at the time such information is collected notwithstanding future changes to this Policy. The practices and policies in this Policy replace all previous notices or statements with respect to the same subject matter. If we make any material changes, we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

### Opt-out or Termination of User Accounts

If users have opted out of all communication with the Website, or deleted/deactivated their account, _Probiotic America, LLC_ will not contact such users again nor will their personal information ever be used by us in any manner.

### Contact Information

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.

You may also contact us at:

**Probiotic America, LLC**   
21900 Burbank Blvd   
3rd Floor   
Woodland Hills, CA 91367   
(866) 803-9895

### Security

We are committed to preventing others from unauthorized access to the personal information you provide to us, and we maintain commercially reasonable procedures and technology designed for this purpose. The Website has reasonable technical and organizational security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of information under our control. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat those security measures or use your personal information for improper purposes.

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information, such as credit card number, that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry, 128-bit SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just "surfing."

While we use 128-bit SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment.

### The Information We Collect

We request information from the user on our secure order form. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. We may store this information securely on our server. We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. If we have trouble processing an order, the information is used to contact the user. We may also use this information to inform you of additional goods and services about which you might be interested or to customize your experience and use of the Website.

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal information unless we provide you with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when its release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our website policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising or other uses.

Our Website's payment gateway is hosted by 1ShoppingCart.com. 1ShoppingCart.com has access to aggregate data about our customers in order to assist 1ShoppingCart.com in analyzing Site performance and making improvements to 1ShoppingCart.com products.

All orders are processed through Network Merchants, LLC. The personal information Network Merchants, LLC acquires in processing payment transactions varies according to the nature of the transaction and the way in which merchants or financial institutions are using their payment services. It may include, for example, the amount of the transaction, the consumer's name, credit card number and expiration date, checking account number, billing address, and shipping address.

Network Merchants, LLC uses the information collected to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, to process payment transactions, to facilitate billing, and otherwise deliver the payment gateway services. Personal information is used to process payment transactions and for no other purpose.

Network Merchants, LLC stores transaction information on secure computers located in a locked data center. Only a small number of employees involved in the management of the data center have physical access to these computers. Where possible, Network Merchants, LLC encrypts information stored on their computers as a further measure of protection. Network Merchants, LLC uses state-of-the-art firewalls and other security technology to prevent their computers from being accessed by unauthorized persons. Information security is critical to our business. Nevertheless, nothing can be 100% secure. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us.

We may ask you for personally-identifying information in connection with a promotion or survey. Any email you receive from us, or third parties authorized by you to send email, will contain additional opt-out or unsubscribe options in the email with instructions on how to unsubscribe from receiving future emails.

We may automatically gather general statistical information about our Website and visitors, such as IP addresses, browsers, pages viewed, number of visitors, goods and services purchased, transactions completed, etc. To do this, we use action tags and cookies provided by our site analytics and marketing partners. Although these partners log the information coming from our site on our behalf, we authorize how that data may and may not be used.

### Children Under 13

We do not knowingly collect or use personal information from children under 13. We have no way of distinguishing the age of individuals who address our Website. If a child has provided us with personal information, the parent or guardian should contact us to remove the information and opt out of promotional opportunities.

### Log Files

Like most standard website servers, we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

### Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags, and scripts are used by _Probiotic America, LLC_ and our partners, affiliates, or analytics or service providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

#### MANDATORY COOKIES

Minimum required for the site to function correctly and securely.

This Website will:

  * Remember page to page information essential for completing forms
  * Remember cookie settings
  * Protect your personal information

#### PREFERENCE AND ANALYTICS

Used to improve your browsing experience.

This Website will:

  * Retain preference settings and geographic information
  * Make sure the Website looks consistent
  * Capture Website usage to further improve experience

#### SOCIAL MEDIA AND ADVERTISING

Enables selected advertising relevant to you.

This Website will:

  * Allow you to share pages with social networks like Facebook, Pinterest, and Twitter, etc.

The use of tracking technologies by our third party [partners, affiliates, service providers] is not covered by our privacy policy. Technology limitations do not enable us direct access or control over such technologies.

### The Way We Use Information

Our goal is to provide products that best meet your needs, therefore we evaluate your personal interactions with us in an effort to bring you the products which best suit your tastes. In addition, we use your information to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings, and to customize our site's content, layout, and services.

We may use your information to deliver information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests, such as targeted banners, new products, services, and promotions. At times, we may ask you to provide us voluntarily with additional information regarding your personal or business interests, experience, or requests, which we may use to customize our products and services for you.

If you place a request for products or services, we use your personal information to ship your order; if the products or services are from a retail partner, we may provide your relevant information to that retailer for purposes of the transaction. If you establish a credit account with us or our providers, we collect additional information, including billing information, credit card number, and expiration date, and tracking information from checks or money orders.

### User Access and Choice

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend, or delete it by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

_MAIL_   
Probiotic America, LLC,   
21900 Burbank Blvd   
3rd Floor   
Woodland Hills, CA 91367   
(866) 803-9895   

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### California Residents

Many browsers have a “Do Not Track” feature that allows you to instruct websites that you do not want them to track your online activities. These browser features are not uniform, so we are not currently set up to respond to this feature.

California residents who have provided their personal information to us may request data regarding disclosures of their information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. Such requests may be submitted to us at:

Probiotic America, LLC,   
21900 Burbank Blvd   
3rd Floor   
Woodland Hills, CA 91367   
(866) 803-9895   

Please specify in your communication that you are making a “California Shine the Light” inquiry. We will respond to your inquiry within 30 days.

### Newsletter

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter may opt-out of receiving these communications by following the instructions on our unsubscribe page.

### Links

The Web site contains links to other sites. _Probiotic America, LLC_ is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites. By including links to other websites, we neither endorse such sites nor guarantee that the information they contain is accurate. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site to read the privacy statements of every linked website as the privacy policies of each may differ from ours. This privacy statement applies solely to the _Probiotic America, LLC_ Website.

### Social Media Widgets

Our Site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook and Twitter buttons and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

### Third Party Advertising

We do not accept any paid advertisements on _Probiotic America, LLC_. Any services or products recommended and/or offered in the newsletter or elsewhere on _Probiotic America, LLC_ have gone through extensive review before such recommendations, and based on that review were recommended and/or offered.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on _Probiotic America, LLC_. Google's use of the remarketing and analytics cookies enables them to serve ads to _Probiotic America, LLC_ users based on their visit to _Probiotic America, LLC_ and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the remarketing cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy preferences](http://www.google.com/settings/ads) or visiting [www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

### Unsolicited Ideas

We welcome feedback, questions, and comments about our products, services, and this Website. As a general policy, we do not accept unsolicited ideas for products or services through this Website. All communications and other materials (including, without limitation, unsolicited ideas, photographs, drawings, suggestions, or materials) you send to this Website by e-mail or otherwise are and shall remain the sole and exclusive property of _Probiotic America, LLC_ and may be used by us for any purpose whatsoever, commercial or otherwise, without compensation to you.
